{
    "level1": [
      {
        "question_id": 1,
        "question_text": "What is RAM?",
        "choice1": "Random Access Memory",
        "choice2": "Read Again Memory",
        "choice3": "Re-Access Memory",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Random Access Memory",
        "level": 1
      },
      {
        "question_id": 2,
        "question_text": "What is Python?",
        "choice1": "Programming Language",
        "choice2": "Database Query Language",
        "choice3": "Both",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Programming Language",
        "level": 1
      },
      {
        "question_id": 3,
        "question_text": "What is HTML?",
        "choice1": "Hypertext Markup Language",
        "choice2": "Hyper Text Transfer Protocol",
        "choice3": "Home Tool Markup Language",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Hypertext Markup Language",
        "level": 1
      }
    ],
    "level2": [
      {
        "question_id": 4,
        "question_text": "What is CPU?",
        "choice1": "Central Processing Unit",
        "choice2": "Central Performance Unit",
        "choice3": "Computer Processing Unit",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Central Processing Unit",
        "level": 2
      },
      {
        "question_id": 5,
        "question_text": "What is JavaScript?",
        "choice1": "Scripting Language",
        "choice2": "Markup Language",
        "choice3": "Programming Language",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Scripting Language",
        "level": 2
      },
      {
        "question_id": 6,
        "question_text": "What is CSS?",
        "choice1": "Cascading Style Sheets",
        "choice2": "Cross-Platform Style Sheets",
        "choice3": "Computer Style Sheets",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Cascading Style Sheets",
        "level": 2
      }
    ],
    "level3": [
      {
        "question_id": 7,
        "question_text": "What is GPU?",
        "choice1": "Graphics Processing Unit",
        "choice2": "Graphics Performance Unit",
        "choice3": "General Processing Unit",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Graphics Processing Unit",
        "level": 3
      },
      {
        "question_id": 8,
        "question_text": "What is SQL?",
        "choice1": "Structured Query Language",
        "choice2": "Standard Query Language",
        "choice3": "System Query Language",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Structured Query Language",
        "level": 3
      },
      {
        "question_id": 9,
        "question_text": "What is Java?",
        "choice1": "Programming Language",
        "choice2": "Scripting Language",
        "choice3": "Markup Language",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Programming Language",
        "level": 3
      }
    ],
    "level4": [
      {
        "question_id": 10,
        "question_text": "What is DNS?",
        "choice1": "Domain Name Service",
        "choice2": "Domain Name System",
        "choice3": "Domain Network Service",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Domain Name System",
        "level": 4
      },
      {
        "question_id": 11,
        "question_text": "What is PHP?",
        "choice1": "Hypertext Preprocessor",
        "choice2": "Hypertext Programming",
        "choice3": "Hypertext Processor",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Hypertext Preprocessor",
        "level": 4
      },
      {
        "question_id": 12,
        "question_text": "What is SSL?",
        "choice1": "Secure Socket Layer",
        "choice2": "Secure System Layer",
        "choice3": "Secure Style Layer",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Secure Socket Layer",
        "level": 4
      }
    ],
    "level5": [
      {
        "question_id": 13,
        "question_text": "What is XML?",
        "choice1": "eXtensible Markup Language",
        "choice2": "eXecutable Markup Language",
        "choice3": "eXtra Markup Language",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "eXtensible Markup Language",
        "level": 5
      },
      {
        "question_id": 14,
        "question_text": "What is Ruby?",
        "choice1": "Programming Language",
        "choice2": "Scripting Language",
        "choice3": "Markup Language",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Programming Language",
        "level": 5
      },
      {
        "question_id": 15,
        "question_text": "What is API?",
        "choice1": "Application Programming Interface",
        "choice2": "Application Process Interface",
        "choice3": "Application Performance Interface",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Application Programming Interface",
        "level": 5
      }
    ],
    "level6": [
      {
        "question_id": 16,
        "question_text": "What is HTTP?",
        "choice1": "Hypertext Transfer Protocol",
        "choice2": "Hypertext Transfer Process",
        "choice3": "Hypertext Test Protocol",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Hypertext Transfer Protocol",
        "level": 6
      },
      {
        "question_id": 17,
        "question_text": "What is C++?",
        "choice1": "Programming Language",
        "choice2": "Scripting Language",
        "choice3": "Markup Language",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Programming Language",
        "level": 6
      },
      {
        "question_id": 18,
        "question_text": "What is SMTP?",
        "choice1": "Simple Mail Transfer Protocol",
        "choice2": "Simple Message Transfer Protocol",
        "choice3": "Simple Mail Testing Protocol",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Simple Mail Transfer Protocol",
        "level": 6
      }
    ],
    "level7": [
      {
        "question_id": 19,
        "question_text": "What is JSON?",
        "choice1": "JavaScript Object Notation",
        "choice2": "JavaScript Oriented Notation",
        "choice3": "JavaScript Order Notation",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "JavaScript Object Notation",
        "level": 7
      },
      {
        "question_id": 20,
        "question_text": "What is C#?",
        "choice1": "Programming Language",
        "choice2": "Scripting Language",
        "choice3": "Markup Language",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Programming Language",
        "level": 7
      },
      {
        "question_id": 21,
        "question_text": "What is FTP?",
        "choice1": "File Transfer Protocol",
        "choice2": "File Testing Protocol",
        "choice3": "File Transfer Process",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "File Transfer Protocol",
        "level": 7
      }
    ],
    "level8": [
      {
        "question_id": 22,
        "question_text": "What is SVG?",
        "choice1": "Scalable Vector Graphics",
        "choice2": "Scalable Video Graphics",
        "choice3": "System Vector Graphics",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Scalable Vector Graphics",
        "level": 8
      },
      {
        "question_id": 23,
        "question_text": "What is Kotlin?",
        "choice1": "Programming Language",
        "choice2": "Scripting Language",
        "choice3": "Markup Language",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Programming Language",
        "level": 8
      },
      {
        "question_id": 24,
        "question_text": "What is DNSSEC?",
        "choice1": "Domain Name System Security Extensions",
        "choice2": "Domain Name System Security",
        "choice3": "Domain Name Security Extensions",
        "choice4": "None Of These",
        "correct_ans": "Domain Name System Security Extensions",
        "level": 8
      }
    ]
  }
  